Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- Band demos and recordings, 1980 1989; Series IV; 77.42 Linear Feet; (78 boxes); 1347 Audiocassettes; 7 Audiotape Reels
  - George Wrage, 1980 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164472)
    Songs transcribed in the liner notes include: "The Other Day" and "Bring Back Disco"
  - Noise Fest, 1981 June; 1 Audiocassette; 01:27:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distprted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164464)
  - Bobby Radcliffe and the Illusion, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164456)
    She Belongs to Me
    Unhh!
    Done Got Over It
    Woke Up Screaming
  - Tirez Tirez, "Social Responsibility", 1986; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164449)
    Set the Timer
    In Your Own Back Yard
    My Mistake
    Paper Boy
    Edge Town
    Wake Up
    See My Problem
    Spin Your Wheels
    Uptight
  - Konk, a Konk demo of sorts for Jim, 1981 June; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio can be heard. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164431)
  - Ludus, "witch's kitchen", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:44:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is in silence from 00:05:29-00:05:53 and 00:26:25-00:26:43. The program is distorted at times. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164423)
  - "Total Access", Ballistic Kisses, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:44:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164415)
    Whose Mama is This
    Recipe for Revolution
    Workaholic
    5 O'Clock World
    Black and Broke
    Domestic Servants
    Body Rhyms
    Tough Shit
    Samuri Toys
  - Francois Kevorkian - Music for the Mind: The Dance, 1981 March 10; 1 Audiocassette; 01:34:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Clicks and pops are present in the program. The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. (Box 58, Item barcode 39002137164407)
  - Pleasure Hounds, "Miami, Anymore, Opus", 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161205)
  - Subterraneans, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. High background noise is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161197)
    Come Closer
    Face Value
    Pink Sand
    Two Versions
    Funny
    Hitch Hike
    Carnival of Souls
    interlude
  - Dumptruck, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161189)
    How Come?
    Repitition
    Things Go Wrong
  - Male Model, "model noise" and "video", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161171)
  - Maroons, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); High frequency noise is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161163)
    No Condition
    Everybody Loves You
    Technicality
    Under the Influence
  - Kane Bros, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161155)
    Spark in the Blue Eye
    Between Two Points
    Skin House
    Some Kind of Right
    Bark
  - The Antoinettes, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161148)
    Black Velvet
    And Where Will I
    A Telltale Heart
    Sad-Eyed Susie
  - Steppin' Razor, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is muffled. The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161130)
  - Red Ants, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); 00:10:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161122)
    Don't Run Away
    Two of a Kind
    Baby I'm Lost
  - The Plugz, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161114)
    Achin'
    Electrify Me
    Touch for Cash
    Rumble
  - Subterraneans, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161106)
  - Richard Thorne and the Side Effects, 1981 February 21; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161098)
    On Our Way to Nowhere
    Junkie for Your Love
    Waiting for the Night
    Why Won't You Love Me All the Way?
  - The Slickee Boys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161080)
    Gotta Tell Me Why
    The Brain That Refused to Die
    Question of Temperature
    Can't Believe
    Jailbait Janet
  - The Automatt, "Rank & File", 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161072)
    Not in Love
    Coyote
    Amanda Ruth
    Sundown
  - Levi Dexter, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is in silence from 00:06:00 until 00:06:18. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161064)
    Get So Excited
    Victim of Cool
    Other Side of Midnight
  - The Go Betweens, "Before Hollywood", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:40:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. There are dropouts in the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161056)
    A Bad Debt Follow
    Two Step, Step Out
    Before Hollywood
    Dusty in Here
    Ask
    Cattle and Cane
    By Chance
    As Long As That
    On My Block
    That Way
  - Lonesome Val, 1986; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 59, Item barcode 39002137161049)
    The Next Big thing
    My Old Front Porch
    Sensitive Girl
    Stevie - live at CBGB 1/23/66
    Queen of Your Dreams
  - Angel Corpus-Christi, "I [Love] NY", 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:55:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161254)
    Cheree
    Blank Generation
    Redondo Beach
    Dream Baby Dream
    The Day John Kennedy Died
    Taxi Driver/New York New York
    Here Today Gone Tomorrow
  - Noch Nights, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:23:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is in silence from 00:11:54-00:12:22. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161247)
  - Ultramarine, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161239)
    All Fall Away
    Sell My John Deere
  - Blurt, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:13:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. The program is in silence from 00:23:30-00:23:51. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Audio is unbalanced. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161221)
    A list of songs from "Friday the 12th", 12" E.P. and Ted Milton is included.
    Cherry Blossom Polish
    Bullets for You
    Deep Frozen Heart
    Enemy Ears
    Nogodada
    Gravespit
    Kill Time
    Dog Save My Soul
    The Fish Needs a Bike
    White Line Fever
    Sharks of Paradise
    Nomads
    Love is Like a Violence
    It's Only Recently That Stalins Have Begun to Roost
  - Deep Six, 1983 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161213)
    Sunny Day
    Open Mind
    I Protect Myself
  - Syd Straw (live Cactus Club), 1988 November 11; 1 Audiocassette; 01:15:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program was recorded at a very high level. Static is present. Audio, at times, has an echo. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161288)
  - The Last Band on Earth, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161312)
    Everybody Wants Her
    Heading Out to Sea
    Kaile
    Hard to Know
    Miserable Day
    Don't Give This Dance No Name
  - Brave Combo - demo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161296)
    Money Can't Buy Everything
    Ay Me Duele
    Can Can
    Our Imagined Image
    Tic Toc
    Do Something Different
    Night
    Merida
    Last Words of Sigmund Freud
  - The Parachute Club - demo, 1988; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161304)
  - Nona Hendryx, 1988; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161270)
    I Wanna Get Thru 2 U
    Don't Start
    All the Way to Heaven
    Lookin' For Love
    Love + Love
  - Persian Gulf, "The Movie", 1986; 1 Audiocassette; 00:40:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161262)
  - Details at Eleven, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161379)
    Music for Secretaries
    Blood Vessel
    Derailed
    Blank Wall
  - Angel and the Drunked Gods, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161361)
    Ain't Easy
  - Living Colour, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161353)
  - Cargo Cult, 1986; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161346)
    Vanishing Point
    Safe to Say
    Quality Control
    The Weather
    Plaid City
    Speech Impediment
    Home Improvements
    Neutral Nations
    Love Rings True
    Cargo Culture
  - Quincy, 1978 November 8; 1 Audiocassette; 00:43:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. The program is in silence from about 00:26:42-00:39:43. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161338)
    Can't Live in a Dream
    Dime Store Lights
    Can't Make the Connection
    Priviledged Few
    In the Vanguard
  - Certain Generals, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static and high background noise are present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 60, Item barcode 39002137161320)
    Red Ledge
    Certain Gen
    Kill + Take
    At Peace
  - The Urban Guerrillas, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. A delay or echo in the audio can be heard. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095189)
    forgotten eggs
    wildboy
    forbidden zone
    sonic rapture
    dizzy
    venus
    sudan
    astronomy
  - OGI, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095171)
    Rock is Old
    Rock's Tar
    Hunky Vision
    OGI
  - Noch Nichts, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095163)
    A Certain Passion
    Open the Door
    Chase
  - Rain Worthington, 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There is a gap in the audio from about 05:18-05:45. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095155)
    Songs included: "Americans" and "Out of Waiting"
  - KMZ, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:31:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is unbalanced from about 01:52--3:43. The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095148)
  - The Public Servants, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095130)
    Beauty Based on Science
    Jungle Hotel (excerpt)
    Hemline
  - Barbara Ess, 1982 February 21; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095122)
    From CBGB (off the board)
  - Hudson, 1982 July 15; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095114)
    Up From hell
    Three x Three
    Fat of the Land
  - Two Nice Girls, 1988; 1 Audiocassette; 00:53:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095098)
    Looking Out
    Money
    Follow
    Getting Close
    My Heart Falls Off
    Kick
    Cristi's Song
    Holland
    Goons
    Sweet Jane / Love and Affection
    Heaven on Earth
    Last 10 Dollars
  - Malaria!, 1981 July 26; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095080)
  - Foreign Legion, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095106)
  - Mr. Baxter, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:29:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Speed fluctuations on the tape are present. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095072)
  - Last Roundup, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095064)
  - Death Comet '85, 1984 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095056)
    Death Comet Drive
    Jean Jean (Zaibatsu)
    Encryption
    Mystic Eyes
    Night Flights
    Sadonation
    big beat
    At the Marble bar
    play loud
    America
    Funky Dream
    Exterior St.
  - Child Bearing Hips, 1988; 1 Audiocassette; 00:31:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095049)
    Mattress
    The Kicker
    What Color
    Trust
    You Make Me Nervous
  - The Corvairs, 1988; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095031)
    Ready to Burn
    Find My Way Home
    Angel
    Hair of the Dog, Salt of the Earth
    1,000 Questions
  - Wake Up and Cry, Angel Corpus-Christi, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 61, Item barcode 39002137095023)
    I Can't Make It
    Never Too Late for Linda
    Love in the Shadows
    Rock and Roll Heart
    Wild Bill
    Wake Up and Cry
  - Young Adults, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. High amounts of hiss and static are present. There is a warble in the program. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110525)
    Meat Rampage
    X-Mas in Japan
    Beer
    Complex World
  - Klō, 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110533)
    You're Chic!
    Weirdo
    Try
    Clown
    Baby Wants a Baby
  - The Dance Soul Force, 1 Audiocassette; 00:44:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110541)
  - The Government, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:04:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program distorted at times. Static can be heard. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110558)
    Songs include "Hemingway Hated Disco" and "Drive My Car".
  - Pylon, 1983 August; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The audio is unbalanced for the last 8 minutes of the program. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110566)
  - Arsenal, 1980 March; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. The first 10 minutes was recorded at a very high level. The last 31 minutes consist of background noise. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110574)
  - Dislocation Dance, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110582)
    You'll Never Never Know
    Remind Me
    San Michelle
    Baby Blue
    Tyrannies of Fun
    Working the Midnight Shift
  - Sayso, 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110590)
    To Catch You If I Could
    Only Half Way There
    Turned Out This Way
  - Michelle Shock, 1988 October 25; 1 Audiocassette; 01:28:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static can be heard. The program is muffled at about 00:41:00 until the end of the program. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110608)
    Recorded at CBGB's live.
  - Da Bodeans, 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110616)
    She's a Runaway
    69 Blues
    Strangest Kind
  - Oh-OK!, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Speed fluctuations are present. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110624)
  - Peter Dayton, 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110632)
    That's the Way
    Like to Get to Know You
    She Loves Me Not
    Breaking Up Inside
    The Only Way to Love You
    Don't Wanna Die
  - Lenny Kaye Connection, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110640)
    Jealousy
    I've Got a Right
    Record Collector
    As I Make Love
    I Cry Mercy
    Luke the Drifter
    Giving It All Up
    Suspension
  - Monomania, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110657)
  - Container, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110665)
    Tired of Me
    3 Wishes
    I Hurt You There
    The Shepherd
    Thank You Sierra
  - Crazy Hearts, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110673)
    4 Minutes to Midnight (Dub)
    Adrenalin Control
    L-I-G-H-T
  - "Cold, Tired, / Hungry", 1 Audiocassette; 01:01:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. High amounts of hiss and a warble can be heard. The program is in silence from 00:05:15-05:05:56. (Box 62, Item barcode 39002137110681)
  - The Yellowjackets, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136777)
  - Chandra "Transportation", 1980 May; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136785)
  - Shield '81, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:35:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136769)
  - Tom Verlaine, 1987 April 26; 1 Audiocassette; 01:23:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts are present in the audio. Static can be heard. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136793)
  - Strange Party, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:04:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program was recorded at a very high level. The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136801)
  - Squalls, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136819)
  - Grupo Pueblo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:35:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Clicks and pops can be heard. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Speed fluctuations are present. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136827)
  - Nitecaps demo, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136835)
  - Raunch Hands, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136843)
  - LMNOP LMNO3, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:38:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program was recorded at a very high level. The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137136850)
  - The Wayfarers!, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137122)
  - Salem 66 "The Well", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:02:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Clicks and pops are present. Dropouts in the audio are present. The program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137130)
  - Dog Eat Dog, 1981 November, 1982 February 5; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137148)
  - Dislocation Dance, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137155)
  - Animals From Outer Space, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 01:00:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137163)
  - Foreign Legion, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137171)
  - Mofungo, "End of the World", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:28:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. The program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002137137189)
  - Prisoners of Beat, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136306)
  - The Scott Miner Band, 1978; 1 Audiocassette; 00:57:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136314)
  - 2 Timers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136322)
  - Kløwy, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. There is a warble in the audio. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136330)
  - Tomboys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136348)
  - Walkie Talkie, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136355)
  - Valves, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136363)
  - Open City, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136371)
  - The Parts, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136389)
  - The Pseudos, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136397)